const questions = [
  {
    question: "Your employer must retrain you when there is a change in…",
    options: ["Change in SOP", "Change in Process or Machine", "Energy control procedure", "All of the above"],
    correct: "All of the above"
  },
  {
    question: "The purpose of a machine guard is to",
    options: ["Protect the operator", "Prevent fires", "Improve efficiency", "Protect the machine"],
    correct: "Protect the operator"
  },
  {
    question: "If a machine guard is loose or missing you should",
    options: ["Use metallic tape to fix the problem", "Use the machine carefully", "Not use the machine until repaired", "Leave the area immediately"],
    correct: "Not use the machine until repaired"
  },
  {
    question: "Storage of compressed gas cylinders must be:",
    options: ["In upright positions", "In a dry area", "In a well-ventilated area", "All of the above"],
    correct: "All of the above"
  },
  {
    question: "I can learn about the hazards of specific chemicals by",
    options: ["Asking a co-worker", "Reading the Material Safety Data Sheet", "Reading science magazines", "Talking to friends about it"],
    correct: "Reading the Material Safety Data Sheet"
  },
  {
    question: "After finishing the job, Who can remove locks and tags?",
    options: [
      " Equipment Operator",
      " Management",
      "Person who placed the locks and tags",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    correct: "Person who placed the locks and tags"
  },
  {
    question: "What is Kinetic energy?",
    options: [
      "Stored in batteries",
      "Energy in motion",
      "Chemical energy",
      "Pneumatic energy"
    ],
    correct: "Energy in motion"
  },
  {
    question: "The first step in Lockout Tagout is",
    options: [
      "Put a lock on the main power source",
      "Bleed off all pressure",
      "Sign all tags",
      "Inform the equipment operator"
    ],
    correct: "Inform the equipment operator"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following components is no longer a part of the Personal Fall Arrest System?",
    options: [
      "Full Body Harnesses",
      "Self-closing, self-latching hardware",
      "Body Belts",
      "Y lanyards"
    ],
    correct: "Body Belts"
  },
  {
    question: "An abrasive wheel is checked for cracks or defects with a…",
    options: [
      "Sound or ring Test",
      "Hit and trial Test",
      "Forward or rewind Test",
      "X-ray machine"
    ],
    correct: "Sound or ring Test"
  }

];

export default questions;
